{
    "id": "ayumihirono",
    "name": "廣野鮎美",
    "yomi": "Ayumi Hirono",
    "text": [
        "こんにちは。部屋のカーテンは緑、お気に入りのぬいぐるみは黄色、最近買ったコートは黒です。",
        "Hello. A curtain in my room is green, my favourite stuffed animal is yellow, a coat I recently bought is black."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Website",
            "href": "https://15hirono.wixsite.com/hironoayumi/"
        },
        {
            "a": "Twitter",
            "href": "https://www.twitter.com/HIRONO_Ayumi_/"
        },
        {
            "a": "Instagram",
            "href": "https://www.instagram.com/10rikera___/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Let's eat gyoza, because",
            "jp": "餃子食べよ",
            "yes": "it's sunny",
            "left": "晴れてるから",
            "no": "my stomach tells me so",
            "right": "胃がそう言ってるから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Let's go to the park, because",
            "jp": "公園行こ",
            "yes": "want to walk with you",
            "left": "歩きたいから",
            "no": "want to talk with you",
            "right": "話したいから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Let's watch the rising sun, because",
            "jp": "朝日見よ",
            "yes": "saw it on the TV yesterday",
            "left": "昨日テレビで見たから",
            "no": "in the mountain now",
            "right": "今山にいるから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Let's go to the book store, because",
            "jp": "本屋行こ",
            "yes": "just found it",
            "left": "見つけたから",
            "no": "it was on the road",
            "right": "落ちてたから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Let's talk, because",
            "jp": "話そ",
            "yes": "my hair has grown",
            "left": "髪が伸びたから",
            "no": "I saw a UFO",
            "right": "UFO見たから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Let's dig potatoes, because",
            "jp": "じゃがいも掘ろ",
            "yes": "haven't ever seen a shooting star",
            "left": "流れ星見たことないしさ",
            "no": "want to go to germany",
            "right": "ドイツ行きたいし"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Chocolate, because",
            "jp": "チョコレート",
            "yes": "it's cold",
            "left": "寒いから",
            "no": "the parcel isn't delivered yet",
            "right": "宅配便が届かないから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Let's go out together, because",
            "jp": "デートしましょう",
            "yes": "the wind brew",
            "left": "風が吹いたから",
            "no": "we like green",
            "right": "緑が好きだから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "I am at the top of the building, because",
            "jp": "ビルのてっぺん",
            "yes": "want to see the sky",
            "left": "空が見たいから",
            "no": "want to see the clouds",
            "right": "雲が見たいから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "A excuse",
            "jp": "口実",
            "yes": "I need some",
            "left": "いる",
            "no": "I don't need",
            "right": "いらない"
        }
    ]
}